Finding Aid for the Stanley Kramer Papers LSC.0161
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Films, (Document Boxes)
  - Domino Killings (original title: The Domino Principle)
    - Production Materials
      - 43. Budget--Estimated Detail. (Box 150)
      - 44. Crank Letters. (Box 150)
      - 45. I.T.C. (Box 150)
      - 47. Location, Contracts (originals). (Box 150)
      - 48. Morse, Terry (Associate Producer/ Production Manager). (Box 150)
      - 49. Movement Lists. (Box 150)
      - 50. MPAA. (Box 150)
      - 51. Music (Miscellaneous Correspondence). (Box 150)
      - 52. Music - Shirley Eikhard (Some Day Soon). (Box 150)
      - 54. Shooting Schedule. (Box 151)
      - 55. Starger, Martin--Correspondence (MARSTAR). (Box 151)
      - 56. Schiff, Hirsch & Levine--Correspondence. (Box 151)
      - 57. Screenings. (Box 151)
      - Werner, Oscar (Box 151)
      - Signed Work Permits. (Box 151)
      - Revised Pages, November 28, 1975. (Box 151)
      - Actors--Weekly Contracts. (Box 151)
      - Actors--Daily & Weekly - Stuntmen. (Box 151)
      - Reviews. (Box 151)
      - Frank Waldman--Correspondence. (Box 151)
      - Production Board picture negatives. (Box 151)
      - Photocopies of titles. (Box 334)
      - Production slides--12. (Box 153)
      - Production notes (bound). (Box 153)
      - Notebook of production sketches (blueprints). (Box 154)
      - Revisions., November 12, 1975. (Box 154)
      - Accordion file--Miscellaneous script revisions. (Box 154)
        Missing - not received from Theatre Arts Department.
      - Record. Some day soon. Theme from The Domino Principle. 3 copies. Shirley Eikhard. (Box 154)
      - Mounted photographs of Ku Klux Klan members., 2 items. (Box 154)
      - Advance Press Info. (Box 334)
    - Scripts
      - First draft:, November 10, 1975. (Box 151)
      - Revised first draft:, January 15, 1976. (Box 151)
      - Final draft:, February 23, 1976. (Box 152)
        NOTE: See Folders, 15. Script Revisions (First Revised - January 15) and 38. Continuities Combined. See also Miscellany.
    - Stills
      - Production stills, (20 packets). 8×10. 18/20 pieces per packet. (Box 334, Box 153, Box 152)
      - 7. Stills., 8 × 10. 40 items. (Box 154)
    - Tapes
      - One 7½ tape - Some Day Soon - Main Title (2:35). (Box 153)
  - Eight Iron Men, 1952.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 5)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph.
    - Dialogue continuity., n.d. (Box 294)
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by Harry Brown(?)., February 16, 1952. (Box 294)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 5)
    - 67 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 4)
    - 31 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 14)
    - 33 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - 49 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 3)
    - 44 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Final Verdict
    - 1. First draft screenplay by Elizabeth Wilson., March 9, 1964. (Box 294)
    - 2. Sale. Columbia Pictures Corporation., December 22, 1967. (Box 294)
  - The 5,000 Fingers of Doctor T., 1953.
    - Final shooting script, annotated, with stills. (Box 6)
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by Allan Scott., January 30, 1952. (Box 294)
    - Dialogue continuity., n.d. (Box 294)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 6)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph.
  - The Four Poster, 1953.
    - Final shooting script, heavily annotated. (Box 5)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Rex Harrison).
    - Folder of awards. (Box 5)
      See also: Box 301.
    - Dialogue continuity., n.d. (Box 295)
    - Script. Final draft: By Allan Scott., August 13, 1951. (Box 295)
    - 6 Storyboards from section labeled Poisoned Brandy. (Box 373, Folder 10)
    - 19 Storyboards from section labeled Sequnce G. (Box 373, Folder 9)
    - 12 Storyboards from section labeled The Daugther's Wedding. (Box 373, Folder 8)
    - 9 Storyboards from section labeled Cod Liver Oil Episode. (Box 373, Folder 7)
    - 6 Storyboards from section labeled Her Son's Death. (Box 373, Folder 6)
    - 15 Storyboards from section labled sequence C. (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - 14 Storyboards from section labeled sequence B. (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - 29 Storyboards from section labeled Nuptual Sequence. (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - Silver Bed Award. (Box 301)
  - Guess Who's Coming To Dinner, 1967.
    - Final draft by William Rose. (Box 79)
    - Final draft, heavily annotated by Stanley Kramer. (Box 79)
    - Final draft, Italian. (Box 79)
    - Poster picture of cast, signed.
      missing December 1985.
    - Radio/TV schedules. (Box 295)
    - Income from picture. (Box 295)
    - dialogue continuity. (Folder 3)
    - Stills, 3 pieces. (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - A Special Kind of Magic, history of the film, Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, by Roy Newquist. (Box 79)
    - Three Academy Award nomination plaques: two for best picture; one for best director. (Box 325)
    - cutting continuity. (Folder 4)
    - Dialogue continuity script. (Box 79)
    - Folder of correspondence on awards. (Box 79)
    - Film clips of Kathy Houghton. (Box 79)
    - Sterling silver plate--Kathy Houghton. (Box 325)
    - Screen Directors' Guild Plaque. (Box 325)
    - Council of Churches of Southern California plaque, 1968. (Box 325)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Columbia Pictures). (Box 80)
    - Production files (Comments - De Vol, Frank). (Box 81)
    - Production files (Editorials - Publicity: Campaign reports). (Box 82)
    - Production files (Publicity: Beck - Wardrobe). (Box 83)
    - Publicity files (Academy Awards publicity material). (Box 84)
    - Rand-McNally book material. (Box 84)
    - Publicity files (Advertisements - New York Times). (Box 85)
    - Publicity files (Radio--Trailers). (Box 86)
    - Magazine clippings. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings. (Box 88)
    - 100 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 89)
    - 225 key set stills. (Box 90)
      See also: Boxes 325, 359.
    - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner promotion tapes. (Box 112)
      Tape recording.
    - Miscellany
      - 1. Two albums - interviews. (Box 334)
      - 2. Cut 1-5, (33 1/3 rpm) (Box 156)
      - 3. Picture Continuity - Reel 1A, November 10, 1967. (Box 156)
      - 4. Dialogue Continuity - Reel 1A, October 28, 1967. (Box 156)
    - Scripts
      - 1. First draft:, January 7, 1967. (Box 155)
      - 2. Final draft (2). (Box 156)
      - 3. Script (3). (Box 156)
        NOTE: See Miscellany.
    - Stills
      - 1. 2 portfolios. Publicity material. (Box 334)
    - Folders
      - 1. Preview Program and Sample Tix. (Box 155)
      - 2. Previews, Premieres. (Box 155)
      - 3. Yankee Magazine - Silhouette of a Wedding by Laurie Hillyer - Story Conflict. (Box 155)
      - 4. Rose, William (writer)--Contract. (Box 155)
      - 5. Kramer, Stanley - Expenses. (Box 155)
      - 6. Insurance. (Box 155)
      - 7. MPAA. (Box 155)
      - 8. Claim - The People Web by M.R. Plunkett. (Box 155)
      - 9. Cast & Crew Sheets. (Box 155)
      - 10. Comments etc. (Box 155)
      - 11. Hackett & Company, Samuel - Auditor, New York. (Box 155)
      - 12. Box Office Receipts. (Box 155)
      - 13. A Distant Light--Correspondence. (Box 155)
    - American Cinema Editors' statue, 1968. (Box 359)
  - The Juggler, 1953.
    - Final shooting script, annotated. (Box 5)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 5)
    - Script. First estimating draft: Screenplay by Michael Blankfort., May 7, 1952. (Box 295)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Kirk Douglas).
    - 14 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 7)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 4)
  - The Happy Time, 1952.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 4)
    - Script. First estimating draft: By Earl Felton., November 27, 1951. (Box 295)
    - Dialogue continuity., n.d. (Box 295)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Charles Boyer).
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 4)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 4)
    - 16 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - 35 Stroyboards (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - 33 stills. (Box 4)
  - High Noon, 1952.
    - Final shooting script with story notes. (Box 6)
    - Script., 1951. (Box 295)
    - Script. Screenplay by Carl Foreman. (Box 295)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 6)
    - Photoplay Magazine award, 1952. (Box 357)
    - File of 50 production stills. (Box 6)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 6)
    - Press Book (Box 131)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Gary Cooper).
    - 20 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - Academy Award nomination plaque for best production, 1952. (Box 301)
    - New York Film Critics plaque. Best Motion Picture, 1952. (Box 301)
    - Life and Ideas, Foreign Press Association plaque. (Box 301)
    - Dialogue continuity., March 3, 1952. (Box 295)
    - National Movie Poll Trophy for High Noon, 1952. (Box 330)
  - Home of the Brave, 1949.
    - Final shooting script, heavily annotated by Carl Foreman. (Box 1)
      (titled High Noon) - working title.
    - 8 Storyboards and 3 Photographs. (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay by Carl Foreman., n.d. (Box 295)
    - Screenplay by Carl Foreman., n.d. (Box 295)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 382, Folder 9)
    - 33 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - Jewish War Veterans Award, large brass plaque, 1949. (Box 360)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars Award, 1950. (Box 356)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (James Edwards).
    - Jewish War Veterans Award, framed, 1949.
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 1)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 1)
      See also: Boxes 336, 356, and 360.
    - Los Angeles Urban League plaque for Home of the Brave, 1950. (Box 120)
    - Urban League of New York, plaque, 1949. (Box 356)
    - Scrapbook: The Champion and Home of the Brave. (Box 336)
    - American Civil Liberties Union award. (Box 336)
  - Inherit the Wind, 1960.
    - Treatment by Earl Felton,, original typescript., March 2, 1958 (Box 27)
    - Photos (production) of S. Kramer. (Box 243)
    - Script, October 21, 1958. (Box 241)
    - Script, (5)., August 13, 1959 (Box 242)
    - Script, August 13, 1959 (Box 243)
    - Story treatment, original typescript, heavily annotated by Earl Felton. (Box 27)
    - Synopsis by Earl Felton, April 3, 1957. (Box 27)
    - Music sketches and lead sheets. (Box 341)
    - First draft screenplay by Nathan Douglas and Harold Smith, September 3, 1958. (Box 27)
    - Final draft screenplay by Nathan Douglas and Harold Smith, September 3, 1958. (Box 27)
    - Cutting continuity. (Box 27)
    - Cutting Continuity (2). (Box 243)
    - Cutting: Dialogue Continuity. (Box 243)
    - Dialogue Continuity (2). (Box 243)
    - Dialogue continuity. (Box 27)
    - 215 production stills. (Box 28)
    - 215 production stills. (Box 29)
    - General Correspondence (folder). (Box 243)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Dialogue continuity.) (Box 30)
    - Production files (Distribution reports - M.P.P.A.) (Box 31)
    - Production files (Music - Publicity: Kaplan). (Box 32)
    - Music score on ten 45 rpm records. (Box 307)
    - 6 record albums. (Box 305)
    - Music notes and timing notes. (Box 307)
    - Music sketches and cue sheets. (Box 308)
    - Music skins. (Box 307)
    - Music cue sheets. (Box 306, Box 307)
    - Production files (Publicity: Thomas - Zagon). (Box 33)
    - Production files (Hollywood Reporter & Variety anniversary issues). (Box 34)
      See also: Boxes 308, 341.
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence Dayton premiers. (Box 124)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Reviews. (Box 124)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Lists of awards. (Box 124)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Play and Original Research Data
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Featurette. (Box 125)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. American Legion. (Box 125)
    - Screen Producers' Guild certificate of nomination for Best Production,, framed., 1960 (Box 305)
    - Press Book (Box 131)
    - Berlin Film Festival Award, bronze platter, 1960.
    - La Tercera Resena Mundial de los Festivales Cinematograficos Award, statue, 1960. (Box 305)
    - 10th International Berlin Film Festival, 2 certificates one of which is framed. (Box 305)
    - 21 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Invitation to a Gunfighter, 1964.
    - First draft teleplay for CBS Playhouse 90 by Hal Goodman and Larry Klein, February 11, 1957. (Box 70)
    - Dialogue continuity. (Box 244)
    - Cutting continuity. (Box 244)
    - Script. Final., June 7, 1963. (Box 244)
    - Master Working Script--Supervisor's. (Box 244)
    - Second draft teleplay by Leslie Stevens, March 7, 1957. (Box 70)
    - First draft screenplay by Alvin Sopinsely, February 14, 1958. (Box 70)
    - First draft screenplay, revised, by Hubert Cornfield, original typescript, heavily annotated, October 1, 1962. (Box 70)
    - Second draft screenplay by James Lee Barrett, original typescript and annotated. (Box 70)
    - Final draft screenplay by Elizabeth and Richard Wilson, June 7, 1963. (Box 71)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Credits). (Box 71)
    - Production files (Continuities - Writers). (Box 72)
  - It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World, 1963.
    - Second draft screenplay, annotated by William and Tania Rose. (Box 60)
    - Second draft revised with script supervisor's annotations. (Box 60)
    - Cutting continuity. (Box 296)
    - Comments. (Box 296)
    - 150 stills, 10½ x 13½. (Box 363)
    - Awards. (Box 61)
    - Wardrobe: miscellaneous pieces worn by cast. (Box 322, Box 323, Box 324)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Budget). (Box 61)
    - Production files (Cast and Crew--Music cues). (Box 62)
    - Production files (Musicians - Publicity). (Box 63)
    - Production files (Screenings--Work schedule). (Box 64)
    - 600 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68)
    - TV and radio spots. (Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68)
    - Orchestra score. (Box 313, Box 314, Box 315, Box 316, Box 317, Box 318, Box 319, Box 320, Box 321)
    - Complete music score. (Box 348, Box 349, Box 350, Box 351)
    - 2 record albums of music for Mad, Mad World. (Box 312)
    - 4 interviews on phonograph records. (Box 312)
    - 175 original pen and ink sketches of the ladder sequence, 8 × 10. (Box 69)
    - 250 process plates, 8 × 10. (Box 69)
      See also: Boxes 313-324, 348, 349, 350, 351, 363, 367.
    - Mad World, side one., undated; yrlsc_161_110_001; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:18:14) 7 inches (Box 110, Case 1)
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Mad World, A-2. (Box 110)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Advertising appropriations (Box 127)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. New York mail order reports (Box 127)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Reviews (Box 127)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Stories (Box 128)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. 70 mm. test print (Box 128)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Tear Sheets (Box 129)
    - Distribution Report (Last report, ), Comments, etc., November 30, 1968 (Box 157)
    - Brillig Production, Limited. Rese, William & Tania. (Box 157)
    - Brillig Productions, Limited. William Rose. Award presented to Stanley Kramer in Cannes, France., Summer 1960. (Box 296)
    - Theatre Opening - Re-issue. (Box 157)
    - Gottlieb, Samuel - New York attorney. (Box 157)
    - Elliot, Walter. (Box 157)
    - Eight record albums of music score. (Box 314)
    - Insurance. (Box 156)
    - Zagon, Aaron & Schiff. (Box 156)
    - United Artists--Correspondence. (Box 156)
    - Sale--Correspondence re. MW. (Box 156)
    - Shooting schedule - Pre-production & Plates, April 5, 1962. (Box 160)
    - Shooting schedule, October 1, 1962. (Box 160)
    - William Morris Incorporated--United Artists Corporation. (Box 296)
    - Publishers' Award Plaque for Mad, Mad World, 1964. (Box 331)
    - Revised shooting schedule to finish:, August 21, 1962-November 6, 1962. (Box 160)
    - Film Effects of Hollywood, Incorporated. (Box 157)
    - Film effects contact - sets. (Box 367)
    - Press clippings. (Box 367)
    - Editorial. (Box 157)
    - Scripts
      - 1. First draft screenplay - Something a little less serious (2). (Box 157)
      - 1a. First draft screenplay. Something a little less serious (1). (Box 158)
      - 2. Second draft. (Box 158)
      - 3. Script (two parts), November 9, 1962. (Box 158)
      - 4. Script., (two parts) (Box 159)
      - 5. Script. (Box 159)
      - 6. Continuity. (Box 159)
      - 7. Combined continuity.
        Missing - not received.
      - 8. Cutting continuity (2). (Box 160)
      - 9. Dialogue continuity (3). (Box 160)
      - 10. S. Kramer personal scripts, numbered 1 and 3. (Box 160)
  - Judgement at Nuremberg, 1961.
    - First draft screenplay, 1960. (Box 35)
    - Final draft screenplay, January 9, 1961. (Box 35)
    - Final draft screenplay, revised, July 7, 1961. (Box 35)
    - Abby Mann re Broadway Play - General Correspondence (folder). (Box 246)
    - Script, (2)., January 9, 1961 (Box 244)
    - Script. Revised final., July 7, 1961. (Box 246)
    - Revised final, July 7, 1961. (Box 245)
    - Final Complete (I. Volkman's). (Box 245)
    - Cutting Continuity (4). (Box 246)
    - Stills, 19 pieces. (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Stills in red leather book (13). (Box 309)
    - Parchment from Donatello - cinematography. (Box 35)
    - Cutting continuity and dialogue continuity files. (Box 35)
    - Dialogue Continuity (6). (Box 245)
    - Saturday Review magazine, December 2, 1961. (Box 35)
    - Music Cue Sheets. (Box 246)
    - Clips. (Box 285)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Credits). (Box 36)
    - Production files (M.P.P.A. - Music). (Box 37)
    - Production files (Music - Publicity). (Box 38)
    - Production files (Shooting schedules). (Box 39)
    - Judgement at Nuremberg, paperback book. (Box 40)
    - Preview (audience) cards. (Box 40)
    - Story outline by Abby Mann, original typescript. (Box 40)
    - First draft screenplay by Abby Mann, original typescript, annotated. (Box 40)
    - Second draft screenplay by Abby Mann, original typescript. (Box 40)
    - Publicity posters. (Box 40)
    - United Artists Corporation (Roxlom) - Financing & Distribution Agreement (folder). (Box 246)
    - 2090 production stills, various sizes. (Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46)
      See also: Boxes 309, 310, 311, 341, 356.
    - Judgment - [Proposed file & outline of trials, ]., April 1973 (Folder 2)
    - Judgment - trials research. (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Framed address of Mayor Willy Brandt, premiere., 1961
    - Recorded interviews on three records. (Box 310)
    - Sale of Judgement at Nuremberg and The Defiant Ones. (Box 109)
      See also: Box 367.
    - Press Book (Box 131)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 35)
    - Screen Directors' Guild plaque for nomination for Best Director and medal for award for Best Director. (Box 309)
    - I.C.C. plaque for Premio al Merito Cinematografico Best Foreign picture,, in velvet case., 1962 (Box 309)
    - Screen Producers' Guild nomination for Best Production award. (Box 309)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews Award. (Box 341)
    - Academy Award plaque for nomination for Best Director. (Box 309)
    - Hollywood Foreign Press Award, 1961.; 3 certificates. (Box 356)
    - Academy Award plaque for nomination for Best Motion Picture, (2), 1961 (Box 309)
    - Scholastic Magazine award for Judgement at Nuremberg. (Box 328)
    - Paperweight: National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1962. (Box 309)
    - Scrapbook of stills, World Premiere, Berlin, 1961. (Box 357)
    - Music sketches and lead sheets. (Box 342)
    - Photocopy of music score. (Box 311)
    - Lyric sheets and music timing and notes. (Box 311)
    - Photocopy of music score. (Box 310)
    - 4 phonograph records. (Box 311)
    - Cigar and cigarette box from the cast and crew, 1961. (Box 309)
    - Script--Final tape draft:, April 5, 1974. (Box 285)
    - Script--Amended first draft:, November 7, 1973. (Box 285)
    - Script--Final tape draft: As broadcast., April 5, 1974. (Box 285)
    - Script--Final tape draft: Annotated., April 5, 1974. (Box 285)
    - Script--First tape draft: Annotated., February 28, 1974. (Box 285)
    - Press clippings. (Box 341)
  - Judgement: The Trial of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - first draft - annotated copy. (Folder 2)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - first draft (another copy). (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - second draft, December 11, 1973. (Folder 3)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - Kramer copy - fina tape draft: ]., January 17, 1973 [1974 (Folder 8)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - tape & block schedule. (Folder 6)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - screenplay by Harry Kleiner - first draft:, October 26, 1973. (Folder 7)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - screenplay by Harry Kleiner - first draft: [director's copy]., October 26, 1973 (Folder 8)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell - trials research (Folder 6)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell - research, September 1973. (Folder 4)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - first tape draft, December 17, 1973. (Folder 4)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell Trial - final tape draft, ]., January 17, 1973 [1974 (Folder 5)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell trial - Kramer copy of first tape draft - annotated [from binder]. (Folder 7)
    - Judgment - Rosenberg & Sobell - New York Times research. (Folder 5)
  - Judgment: The Court Martial of the Tiger of Malaya - General Yamashita
    - Judgment - Yamashita - New York Times research. (Folder 3)
    - Script--First draft: Screenplay by Norman Corwin., October 26, 1973. (Box 285)
    - The Court Martial of General Yamashita, (Various revisions). (Box 285)
    - The Court Martial of General Yamashita, (List of witnesses not included in First draft). (Box 285)
    - Judgment: The Court Martial of General Yamashita, (General revisions). (Box 285)
    - Scripts
      - 1. Calley original. (Box 161)
      - 2. S. Kramer's original script. (Box 162)
      - 3. Lt. Calley, By John Sack., June 24, 1971. (Box 162)
      - 4. Second draft:, July 2, 1974. (Box 162)
      - 5. Second draft:, July 2, 1974. (Box 162)
      - 6. Final tape draft:, August 13, 1974. (Box 162)
      - 7. Revised script, n.d. (Box 162)
      - 8. As Broadcast script, January 12, 1975. (Box 163)
      - 9. First draft. Henry Denker. (2)., November 1, 1973 (Box 163)
    - Miscellany
      - 1. Poster. (Box 354)
      - 2. Clips--Lt. Calley. (Box 176)
      - 3. Manuscript (John Sack's). (Box 176)
      - 4. New York Times news articles, bound. (Box 176)
    - Transcripts (Calley vs. U.S. Army).
      - 1. vol. 1, Book 1 (2). (Box 163)
      - 2. vol. 1, Book 2 (2). (Box 164)
      - 3. vol. 1, Book 3., (approximately 700 pp.) (Box 164)
      - 4. vol. 1, Book 4. (Box 164)
      - 5. vol. 2, Book 1: Index (2). (Box 165)
      - 6. vol. 3, Book 1: pp. 1-527 (2). (Box 165)
      - 7. vol. 3, Book 2: pp. 528-917 (2). (Box 166)
      - 8. vol. 3, Book 3: pp. 918-1073. (Box 166)
      - 9. vol. 3, Book 3: pp. 918-1342. (Box 167)
      - 10. vol. 3, Book 3: pp. 1074-1342. (Box 167)
      - 11. vol. 3, Book 4: pp. 1343-1783. (Box 167)
      - 12. vol. 3, Book 4: pp. 1369-1805. (Box 168)
      - 13. vol. 3, Book 4: pp. 1343-1793. (Box 168)
      - 14. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 1794-2305. (Box 168)
      - 15. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 1806-1913. (Box 169)
      - 16. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 1914-1990. (Box 169)
      - 17. vol. 3, Book 5: pp. 1991-2067. (Box 169)